Guide to the Stanford University, Planning Office, Records SC0486
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2007-075
  - Building Reuse and Site Studies for Hoover Pavilion and Children's Hospital at Stanford. Sandy & Babcock Architects Planners Oct. 1, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University Medical Center Regional Plan Evaluation. Watkins Carter Hamilton Architects. December 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Traffic Study, Mayfield/Mayfield intersection, Oct. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Traffic counts, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Traffic Impact Study for Medical Plaza Building D, Dec. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Traffic profile, Junipero Serra, Nov.-Dec. 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Traffic Study, Dec. 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Traffic - Level of Service Analysis, Technical Appendix, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Traffic - Level of Service Analysis, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Traffic - Level of Service Analysis, May 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Traffic - Sand Hill Road intersections analysis, June 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Traffic - Level of Service Analysis, May 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Transit Plan, Feb. 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Hillview-Porter Area, Site Safety Plan for Remedial Investigation/Feasibility Study Activities, ENSR Document No. 3457-001-620, May 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - DAPER, Eastern Sector Plan, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Doty, Andy, " The Stanford Land Endowment: An Endangered Resource," text with cover letter, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Hoover House - printed scans of photos and plans, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - J. E. Nelson, Stanford land use, historical (1) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - J. E. Nelson, Stanford land use, historical (2) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - J. E. Nelson, Stanford land use, historical (3) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Preliminary Development Sduy, Portion of the Lands of Stanford Universty [for housing development], March 1953 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate Handbook, ca. 1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Report on Master Plan by President's Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, June 1954 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Skidmore, Owings & Merrill, Master Plan, final draft (no date) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Research Park, Strategic Plan Draft, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Research Park - handbook and brochure (Stanford Management Company) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Research Park Feasibility Study 1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Stanford University architecture and history - assorted published articles (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Master Plan, Stanford University Medical Center, Bertrand Goldberg Associates, May 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University Medical Center Site & Floor Plans, SUMC Facilities Department, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2008-087
  - 1990 Consultant Selections (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1991 Consultant Selections (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1992 Consultant Selections (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1993 Consultant Selections (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1994 Consultant Selections (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1995 Consultant Selections (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1996 Consultant Selections (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Three Year Agreement - Office Architects Selections, 1997-98 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Accessory Structures Design Competition (Kiosk) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bakewell & Brown Buildings - Reuse Study Consultant Selection, 1992-96 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Carnegie Foundation - Architect Selection, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chemistry Dept. Space Study - Architect Selection, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cooksey House Study - RFP/Architect Selection, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CPPC (Career Planning and Placement Center), 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CPPC (Career Planning and Placement Center) (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - FEMA Projects - Consultant Selection Documentation, 1989-95 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Re: FEMA Consultants, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Earthquake Restoration Projects - Pre-Qualification Selections, 1989-90 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
  - Hill Houses Architect Selection, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
  - Mechanical Engineering Space Study - Architect Selection Program, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - New Guinea Sculpture Garden - Landscape Architect Selection, 1991-92 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Old Chemistry, RFP, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Parking Plan Analysis - Consultant Selection, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - SRP [Stanford Research Park] Land Use Plan/Guidelines Planner Selection, 1991-92 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - Performing Arts Center Feasibility Study - Consultant Selection, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
  - SUMC Design Guidelines Consultant Selection, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - SUMC Region Plan - Planning Consultant Selection, 1991-93 (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
  - Stanford West - Architect Selection, 1986-92 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - SMC Stanford West Apts (Architect Selection), 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Tower House Historic Restoration and Adaptive Reuse, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Project 2343 - Student Activities Space Master Plan, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Project 3709 - DAPER Admin/Encina Gym Re-Use Study Consultant Selection, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - Project 3919 - NWC (Near West Campus) Redevelopment - Phase 2, Design/Architectural Competition (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - Project 3919 - Near West Campus Redevelopment - Phase 2, Short List Architects' Slides (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Project 3919 - NWC Models/Renderings/Plans of all Presentations [slides] (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Planning, Set 2: Science & Engineering Quad/Hewlett-Packard Slide Show, (10 April 1995) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Project 3919M - McCullough Renovations Architectural Selection, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Project 3919M - McCullough Building Renovations: Request for Architectural, Engineering, and Programming Services Proposal, (March 8, 1995) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Project 3997 - Terman Engineering Remodel - Architect Selection, 1995-96 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Project 4019 - Serra Mall Sculpture - Artist Selection, 1995-96 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Project 4022 - Mitchell Earth Sciences Seismic Strengthening - Architect Selection, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
  - Project 4022 - Mitchell Earth Sciences Building Seismic Strengthening, (May 16, 1996) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Project 4038 - Margaret Jacks Hall - Architect Selection, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
  - Project 4208 - Bldg 02-500 Seismic Rehab - Architect Selection, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Project 4209 - Parking Structure 4 - Program/Site Consultant Selection, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Project 4216 - Art Gallery/Cumming Art Analysis/Planning Study - Consultant Selection, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Project 4216 - Art Gallery and Cummings Art Facilities Analysis and Space Planning Study, (March 27, 1996) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Project 4221 - Four Community Centers Accessibility Survey - Architect Selection, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Project 4224 - Alway Bldg, Genetics Labs Renovation - Architect Selection, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Project 4224 - Alway Bldg, Genetics Labs Renovation - Request for Architectural, Engineering, Services Proposal, (April 22, 1996) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Project 4243 - Hopkins Site Analysis & Program - Consultant Selection, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Project 4243 - Hopkins Marine Station Site Inventory and Analysis - Professional Services Proposal, (April 17, 1996) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Project 4262 - Memorial Hall Programming - Architect Selection, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Project 4266 - Bonair Siding Facilities Analysis & Site Study - Consultant Selection, 1995-96 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Project 4251 - Main Quad Environmental Graphics - Consultant Selection, 1995-96 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Project 4267 - Community Outreach Consultant Selection, 1994-95 (Box 6, Folder 10-11)
  - Project 4270 - GSB Space Planning Consultant Selection, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Project 4293 - Education Building Program and Renovations - Architect Selection, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Project 4293 - Education (Cubberly) Building Program and Renovations - Request for Architectural/Engineering Program and Design Services Proposal, July 24, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Project 4560 - Edwards Building Replacement Design Competition, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Project 4259 - Edwards Building, Neurosciences Faculty & Staff Offices - Architect Selection, 1996-97 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Project 4259 - Edwards Building - Neurosciences Faculty and Staff Offices Renovations - Request for Architectural/Engineering Program and Design Services Proposal, November 27, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Project 4303 - Jasper Ridge Site Analysis (Consultant Selection), 1997-98 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Project 4384 - Meyer-Buck Estate Program and Renovations - Architect Selection, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Project 4427 - Expanded Aquatics Complex - Architect Selection, 1997-98 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Project 4427 - Expanded Aquatics Complex - Request for Professional Services, January 22, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Project 4446 - Bio-Chem Annex - Lab Design & Architect-of-Record, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
  - Project 4446 - Bio-Chem Annex - Lab Design & Architect-of-Record, 3 of 4, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Project 4764 - Photonics Laboratory - Architect Selection, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Project 4891 - Old Bookstore/Career Planning & Placement Center Renovation & Possible Addition, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Project 6050 - Hanna House Restoration - Architect Selection, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Project 6074 - Museum Restoration - Architect Selection, 1990-93 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
  - Project 6120 - Bldg 1-250 Seismic Rehab - Architect Selection, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Project 6120 - Building 01-250 Seismic Strengthening Request for Programming and Architectural/Engineering Design Services, July 30, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Project 7435 - Lagunita Seismic Upgrade and Renovations - Architect Selection, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Project 7435 - Lagunita Court Programming, Schematic Design, and Prototype Renovation to Granada Hall, Request for Programming and Architectural/Engineering Design Services, October 7, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Project 7502 - Cowell Cluster Renovations - Architect Selection, 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Project 7502 - Cowell Cluster Renovations - Request for Professional Programming and Architectural Design Services, January 15, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Project 9405 - Page Mill/JSB Sound Wall Landscape Arch Selection, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Project 4262 - Memorial Auditorium Rens - Architect Selection [contents are really on a variety of projects] (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Project 4262 - Memorial Auditorium Rens - Architect Selection [content here is Mem Aud], 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Stage Design Competition, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Sightline: Proposal for Stanford University Commencement Stage - Conceptual Design Study, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Planview, Inc. for Innovents/Stanford: Preliminary Sun Screenside Elevation, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Stage for Stanford University: Conceptual Design Study, (May 1999) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Sparks: Commencement Stage Proposal (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Stanford University Commencement Stage Conceptual Design Study, by Innovents LLC (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Project 3013B - CISX - 1993 Edition - Architect Selection (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - CISX Competition Slides (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Project 3908 - Stadium Improvements - Architect Selection, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Project 3938 - H&DS Graduate Housing Architect Competition, 1994-96 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Project 3938 - 1996 Graduate Housing at Governor's Corner - Competition Slides (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Project 3938 - 1996 Graduate Housing At Governor's Corner - Short List Slides (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Project 3899 - Center for Cancer & Neurological Research Design Competition, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Project 3899 - Center for Cancer & Neurological Research Design Competition, 1994-95 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Center for Cancer and Neurosciences Research, Project 3899: Conceptual Design and Professional Services Proposal, September 11, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Project 3899 - CCNR Competition Slides - Davis/Brody, ZGF, & Existing Conditions Model (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Project 3899 - CCNR - Competition Slides - Foster (Model) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Project 3899 - More CCNR Slides (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Project 3899 - CCNR - Slides of Short-List Firms (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Project 3899 - CCNR - Competition Slides - Foster (Boards) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Project 3965 - GSB Housing Architect Competition, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 8-10)
  - Hospitality Design Magazine: Gold Key Awards, (11/94) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Hospitality Design Magazine: Hotel Company of the Year, (12/94) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Project 3965 - Graduate School of Business Residential Learning Center: Conceptual Design Study & Professional Services Proposal, (April 24, 1995) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Project 3965 - GSB Residential Learning Center - Competition Slides (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
  - Project 3965 - GSB Housing Short-List Slides (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Project 4270 - GSB Expansion Architectural Competition, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
  - Project 4270 - Graduate School of Business - Littlefield Expansion: Request for Conceptual Design and Professional Services Proposal, (Oct 15, 1996) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Project 4270 - Graduate School of Business Space Planning Study: Professional Services Proposal, (June 7, 1996) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Project 4270 - GSB Expansion Slides - Design Competition (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Project 4270 - GSB/Littlefield Expansion - Competition Slides (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Project 4480 - Escondido Village Infill - Design Competition, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Project 4480 - Escondido Village Infill - Design Competition (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - BRU Architects - Re: Escondido Village Infill Housing - Design Competition, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Escondido Village Infill Housing: Design Competition Requirements (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Project Formulation for: Escondido Village Graduate Student Housing - SWA Group Draft, (August 1998) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Escondido Village Infill Design Competition Slides, (1998) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Project 4455 - Alumni Center Landscape Design Competition, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Guzzardo & Assoc., Inc.: Proposal for Landscape Architecture Services for Alumni Center, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Project 4455 - Stanford University Alumni Center Landscape: Conceptual Design Study & Professional Services Proposal, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Ron Wigginton/Land Studio: Stanford University Alumni Center Landscape - Conceptual Design & Services Proposal, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - SWA - Alumni Center Landscaping (Project 4455) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Communications & Community Outreach Plan - Consultant Selection, 1995-96 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Project 4503 - Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve Consultant Selection: The Colyer Freeman Group, Architects (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Project 4503 - Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve Consultant Selection: Rob Wellington Quigley, FAIA, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Project 4503 - Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve Consultant Selection: Lyndon/Buchanan Associates, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Project 4503 - Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve Consultant Selection: Hart/Howerton Architects, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - San Luis Sustainability Group: Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve, Biennial Report, 1996-98 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Project 4521 - Cowell Health Center Replacement - Design Competition, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Hawley, Peterson, & Snyder Architects: Proposal for Architectural Services, Cowell Student Health Center, (May 2000) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Project 4521 - Hawley, Peterson, & Snyder Architects: Statement of Qualifications, Student Health Center Replacement, (March 2000) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Cowell Student Health Center Replacement Project: Proposal for Professional Services and Conceptual Design Flad & Associates, (May 2000) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Project 4560 - Edwards Building Replacement - Design Competition, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Project 4560 - Boora Architects, Re: Edwards Building Replacement Project (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Project 4560 - Skidmore, Owings, & Merrill (SOM), Re: Edwards Building Replacement Project (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Stanford School of Medicine: Medical Education Building: Boora Architects, (Dec 1999) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Project 4793 - Maples Renovations - Architect Selection, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Roscoe Maples Pavilion Renovations: Request for Proposal, (2/02) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Project 6104 - Stanford Museum Restoration - Architect Competition, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
  - Stanford Art Museum Restoration & Expansion Written Proposal, (April 1994) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Project 6104 - Stanford Art Museum Restoration & Expansion - Short- List Architects Slides (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Museum Restoration Design Competition Slides: Graphics/Models (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Project 6123 - Stanford Student Services Building - Design Competition, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cody Anderson Wasney Architects, Re: Proposal for Architectural Services for Student Services Building (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Proposal for Architectural Design Services - Student Services Building (Siegel & Strain Architects), June 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Siegel & Strain Architects - Qualifications for Student Services Building Project (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Proposal For Student Services Building (Page & Turnbull, Inc.) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Stoecker & Northway Architects, Inc., Re: Student Services Building Project (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Project 9602 - Main Quad Oval Landscape Arch Competition, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Project 9602 - Main Quad "Oval" Reconstruction, Serra Mall - Phase 3: Conceptual Design Study & Professional Services Proposal, (Feb 1996) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Main Quad Environmental Graphics Program - Skidmore, Owings, & Merill (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Project 9602 - Oval Competition Slides (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Response to Request for Proposal: Main Quad ÒOvalÓ Reconstruction (Serra Mall - Phase 3), by Peter Walker, William Johnson & Partners, (March 1996) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - The SWA Group: Main Quad "Oval" Reconstruction (Serra Mall - Phase 3), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Proposal for Main Quad "Oval" Reconstruction (Serra Mall - Phase 3), by Tom Richman & Associates, (March 1996) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Professional Services Proposal for Reconstruction of the Oval, by Sebastian & Associates, (March 1996) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Project 6565 - Ambulatory Care Center - Design Competition, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
  - Project 6565 - Ambulatory Care Building - Conceptual Design and Professional Services Proposal, (May 1996) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Health Services: Ambulatory Care Building Program Addendum, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Presentation Leavebehind: Stanford Health Services Ambulatory Care Building, by BTA (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Project 6565 - Ambulatory Care Center - Design Competition Long List/Short List (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Project 6565 - Ambulatory Care Center Competition Slides (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Stadium Feasibility Study (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Preliminary Stanford Stadium Program & User Group Meeting Notes, (August 2001) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Stadium - Final Existing Conditions Report, (Oct 2001) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Stadium - Existing Conditions Report, (Sept 2002) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Ambulatory Care Building, by Kaplan McLaughlin Diaz, (June 1996) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Architectural Drawings: Ambulatory Care by Polshek, (1996) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University Medical Center: Ambulatory Care Building, by KMD (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2008-194
  - UCLBD (Stanford University Committee on Land and Building Development)-Volume 1 (folder 1 of 3), 11/1984-6/1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - UCLBD-Volume 1 (folder 2 of 3), 7/1985-4/1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - UCLBD-Volume 1 (folder 3 of 3), 5/1986-10/1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - UCLBD-Volume 2 (folder 1 of 3), 11/1986-3/1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - UCLBD-Volume 2 (folder 2 of 3), 4/1987-10/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - UCLBD-Volume 2 (folder 3 of 3), 11/1987-2/1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - UCLBD-Volume 3 (folder 1 of 3), 3/1988-9/1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - UCLBD-Volume 3 (folder 2 of 3), 10/1988-4/1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - UCLBD-Volume 3 (folder 3 of 3), 5/1989-11/27/1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - UCLBD-Volume 4 (folder 1 of 2), 1/1990-3/1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - UCLBD-Volume 4 (folder 2 of 2), 4/1990-12/1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - UCLBD-Volume 5 (folder 1 of 2), 1/1991-10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - UCLBD-Volume 5 (folder 2 of 2), 11/1991-11/1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - UCLBD-Volume 6 (folder 1 of 3), 1/1994-10/1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - UCLBD-Volume 6 (folder 2 of 3), 11/1994-10/1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - UCLBD-Volume 6 (folder 3 of 3), 1/1996-5/1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - UCLBD-Volume 7 (folder 1 of 4), 9/1998-1/2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - UCLBD-Volume 7 (folder 2 of 4), 2/2001-5/2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - UCLBD-Volume 7 (folder 3 of 4), 10/2003-3/2005 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - UCLBD-Volume 7 (folder 4 of 4), 4/2005-11/2007 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Charge to the Committee on Land and Building Development (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Plan for Athletics, Physical Education & Recreation (Summary), 9/1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Museum-Turnbull Study, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - FEMA-Appeals, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Land & Buildings Committee-Project Tour, 12/10/1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Plaques & Commemorative Objects on Campus (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University Ten Year Seismic Strengthening and Restoration Program: National Preservation Awards, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - SLAC-Comprehensive Site Plan, 4/28/2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - SLAC-Long Range Development Plan Committee, 1/2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University Main Quad Balustrade and Terra Cotta Urns Restoration, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University Campus Center-Exterior Space Program Study-Final Report (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The Leland Stanford Junior Museum of Art Stanford University-Historic Structure Report, 10/1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Regional Planning of the Stanford Campus, September 1988, 9/1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Free-Standing Arcades-Report on October 17, 1989 Earthquake Damage and Proposed Repair, 10/1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Hanna House Stanford University Programming Document, SU Project Number 6110, 5/31/1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Encina Gymnasium-Feasibility Report, 10/1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Stanford University Art Museum Feasibility Study: Post Earthquake Renovations and Additions, Draft, 9/25/1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Clark Center Space Planning and Massing Design Process, 2/14/2000 (Box 3)
  - Clark Center Design Process, 3/20/2000 (Box 3)
  - Clark Center Scheme V Design Process, 5/26/2000 (Box 3)
  - Clark Center Scheme V Design Process, 6/6/2000 (Box 3)
  - Clark Center Scheme V Design Process, 6/26/2000 (Box 3)
  - Clark Center Design Process, 8/7/2000 (Box 3)
  - Clark Center Design Process, 9/11/2000 (Box 3)
  - Clark Center Design Process (With letter of transmittal), 10/17/2000 (Box 3)
  - Clark Center Design Process (Color), 10/17/2000 (Box 3)
  - Clark Center Stanford University Design Report, 10/2000 (Box 4)
  - Clark Center November Work Session, 11/13/2000 (Box 4)
  - Clark Center January Work Session, 1/15/2001 (Box 4)
  - Clark Center February Work Session, 2/12/2001 (Box 4)
  - Clark Center March Work Session, 3/12/2001 (Box 4)
  - Clark Center May DD Review, 5/14/2001 (Box 4)
  - Stanford University Clark Center Schematic Design (Box 4)
  - Science, Engineering, and Medical Campus Plan Space Audit, 5/9/2003 (Box 5)